Download Asian Drama, Movies and Shows @ MkvDrama.Com
(Previously)
Am I wrong to be worried about you?
You don't need to worry about me.
It's your fault, you know.
Why did you want me to be your wife?
Arya.
It's me, Tristan.
I have left everything behind.
I want to focus on you, Inggit.
I love Tristan.
What happened?
I just wanted to make my parents happy.
Is it wrong, Iim?
Whom did you marry?
Im.
Yes, I'm Inggit's
legally wedded husband.
Im. Iim.
Oh, my gosh! What should we do now?
Hey, everything will be fine.
Okay, Inggit?
Oh, my gosh.
Yes, Im.
Thank you
for understanding the situation.
But we should wait until she's ready.
That depends. If Inggit's ready,
maybe the situation would be different.
Thanks again, Iim.
To me, you are a good friend to Inggit.
Thank you, Im.
Arya. So how was it?
It's done.
We talked about it. Everything is clear.
Iim understood everything.
But did she promise not to tell anyone
about this?
She promised.
She was just shocked and passed out
for a bit. She was shocked.
You can sit down now.
I want to continue our discussion
from this afternoon.
Before I start, here are
some reading materials for you...
about collective moral autonomy.
There will be a connection to that,
but you can study that yourself.
Okay.
Human beings need to know
about the scale of priorities.
You...
as a human being,...
need to know your place.
Okay.
About...
me, you, and Tristan...
But do you remember your own words...
that I can still keep in touch
with Tristan?
This is not about you being allowed
to keep in touch with Tristan or not.
You can keep in touch with him.
But this is about knowing your place.
What do you mean?
- Who are you?
- Me?
I'm Inggit.
You are my wife.
Daughter of your parents.
So don't let your relationship
with Tristan...
make you forget those identities.
Oh, my gosh. This is so complicated.
What are you saying?
- What is it, Arya?
- Listen.
Does maintaining your relationship
with Tristan...
still makes you a daughter
of your parents?
- It still does.
- Still makes you my wife?
It still does, right?
That's what I'm talking about.
That's what I meant
by knowing your place.
So... Oh, my gosh.
Arya, this is so complicated.
I don't understand.
Let me just ask you this.
If I want to call Tristan to apologize
about what happened earliere, can I?
This is life.
Okay? Welcome to life.
I told you this is not about you
being allowed to or not.
This is about knowing your place.
Knowing your priorities. Understood?
Just tell me clearly.
Okay, I will give you a chance.
Go ahead and call Tristan.
Five minutes.
After that, read this.
Oh, my gosh.
I just want to make a call.
Why is it like tutoring for a thesis?
♪You are supposed to lecture me♪
♪But then you stopped and looked at me♪
♪I still can’t believe
How far you could see♪
♪All of the care that you displayed♪
♪All of the charming things
That you said♪
♪Somehow made me think
That we are meant to be♪
♪You make me feel every love in me♪
♪You let me heal from my history♪
♪Now you have found your way
Into my heart to stay♪
♪Your passion in me♪
♪Has turned out to be♪
♪The reason
That I've been made complete♪
=My Lecturer My Husband=
Thank you very much.
Yes, I've received your chicken dish.
It was really good.
You are the best when it comes
to cooking chicken.
The sambal was really spicy.
Yeah.
Honey? Oh, my gosh. Honey?
Tris! Tristan!
What's wrong, Dave?
- This is bad, Tristan.
- What's wrong, Dave?
- It's Professor Adi...
- What happened to Professor Adi?
Professor Adi has just passed away...
because of Covid.
So all of us have to be isolated now.
Thank you, Dave.
Are you alright?
(I am now Covid patient suspect.
Awaiting for the rapid test result.)
(Let's hope the result is good.)
Oh, my God.
Inggit.
What is it, Inggit?
Poor Tristan.
I'm afraid he is infected with Covid.
He's still a suspect, right?
There's still a chance
he's non-reactive.
- You need to calm down.
- Yeah, but...
- I know, I know. I understand.
- He's close...
But you need to calm down first.
Pray for him that he's okay.
He's still young.
He should be much more...
I'm sure he has a better
immunity system.
Oh, my gosh. Mom is calling.
I wonder what has happened.
Hello, Mom?
Oh, my God!
Dad fell down!
- Mom? Yes, okay. Calm down.
- Oh, my gosh.
Inggit and I will drive
to Yogyakarta tonight. Okay?
Okay. Calm down.
- Don't panic.
- Oh, my gosh.
I will be on my way shortly.
- Bye.
- Arya, we're going now, right?
Let me prepare everything here first.
(My rapid test result is reactive.)
What is it?
- My fear was right...
- Inggit, it's all right.
You're not going through this alone.
Okay?
Inggit, you don't have to go
through this alone, okay?
I'm here.
I promise
that I will always be by your side.
Listen. I will prepare everything
that we need for Yogyakarta.
You just calm yourself down.
I will pack the clothes and everything
we need to bring to Yogyakarta. Okay?
Oh, my gosh.
Inggit?
Hey.
Don't think about it too much.
Everything will be okay.
Inggit, stop looking at your phone.
I can't reach Tristan.
I told you he will be fine.
Just rest now, and try again tomorrow.
- I can't.
- You can, just try to sleep.
Okay?
Come on, try to sleep.
And pray for your father, too.
I can't.
Try. I know you can.
Get some rest.
Think about your father's health too.
It's the most important thing now.
This is the best you got?
Stop disturbing me!
- Come on, Inggit, beat your dad.
- Yes.
Don't tease me like that.
I have to focus.
- You’re making excuses.
- I'm telling the truth.
You always cheat when we play together.
- You did this on purpose.
- Just pick one.
Dad! It's shaking!
Inggit.
I lost again!
Dad keeps on teasing me! He's cheating!
Cheating? It's my turn to win.
- Gosh!
- Cheater!
I'll help you to tickle him.
- You cheat.
- What are you helping her?
So what?
You really are daddy's favorite girl.
Yes.
I love you so much, kid.
Me, too.
I love you so much.
I love you, too.
Hello.
Hello, Wendy?
Sorry to bother you at this hour.
Wen,...
can you please check...
Professor Gunawan's phone number,
from the medical faculty?
Correct.
Or try to contact Prof. Budi...
I'm sure he has the number.
Alright. Please help.
Okay, as fast as possible, please.
This is urgent.
Yeah.
Yes. Okay.
Thank you.
I need to use the bathroom.
Shall we have breakfast too?
I'm not hungry.
No, you have to eat.
You have to take your medicine.
I need to drink some coffee, too.
- Okay.
- I need to stay awake. Come on.
Oh my gosh. Tristan.
Feel so sad for him.
My god.
Learn some manners.
You, too. Learn some manners.
- Have you seen this?
- Yeah, I did.
- Me too.
- We should tell Inggit, right?
Should we tell her?
- Why don't we call Inggit?
- Yeah, let's call her.
- Hello?
- Hello, Inggit.
You must be really sad right now.
I don't know what to do, I'm confused.
Be strong, okay?
I'm sending hugs to you.
Can we come to your house?
We're safe, we never left the house.
Yeah, at least you won’t be alone.
We will stay with you until you get
some good news from Tristan.
I'm not at home, I...
My father is ill,
I’m on the way to Jogja.
I'm having breakfast right now.
How? With whom?
I thought public transportation
wasn’t operational right now.
Are you alright? Are you safe?
Yeah, you should've told me.
You could’ve used my car.
"Sir"? Who is that with you?
- Who is that?
- Hello? Git?
- Hello? You're breaking up.
- Hello?
I think I have bad reception,
I'm losing you.
- Talk to you later.
- Inggit?
- Git?
She hung up.
Inggit, eat up.
Or should I order more food?
Come on, eat up.
So you’ll be healthy
when you see your father.
I swear,
I can feel something isn’t right.
She's been acting really strange lately.
Since I went over to her place,
she's been acting very different.
Maybe because she has to take care
of her sick father, but...
Yeah, I feel that way too.
It's like she's trying to hide something
from us.
What do you think?
Let's just wait for her to call us back.
You're right.
Let's not get ahead of ourselves.
Just keep the change. Thanks.
Everything okay?
Why isn't anyone answering at a time
like this? It's stressing me out.
- Maybe they're busy.
- How come all of them are busy?
Mom and Tristan are not answering.
What are they doing?
I told you not to worry about Tristan.
He must be okay.
Arya.
How likely is it for a person
to be cured from Covid?
How should I know that?
But you read a lot.
But to know the exact number...
I don't know how to answer that,
I might be wrong.
Then, what should I do?
Hello. Good afternoon, Professor.
Yes.
Thank you so much.
Sorry for troubling you.
Yes, she's here.
Thank you. She's right here with me.
Right, hold on.
Who is it?
Hello?
(Prof. Gunawan)
Hello.
How are you doing?
- Are you okay?
- Inggit.
You called Prof. Gunawan?
I just wanted to know your condition.
- Are you okay?
- I'm okay. Thanks for calling.
Thank God. At least you're okay.
Stay healthy, okay?
Just calm down, I'm isolating myself
at the boarding house.
Yes, Prof. Gunawan is here.
- I just want to say that.
- Okay, thanks.
- Stay safe.
- Alright.
Bye.
Let's go.
Arya.
Thanks for helping me out.
Sorry I’ve been troubling you.
You're welcome. Come on.
Professor. Thank you so much.
My girlfriend must be panicking
because she can't call me.
But...
How did Inggit know your number?
Tristan...
you just rest here, okay?
All your friends are rooting for you.
Yes, Prof. Thank you.
Don’t worry about it.
- Just get some rest.
- Yes.
Mom!
Inggit.
Stop, don't hug her yet.
Don't hug her yet.
Sorry. But we just came from outside.
So we need to shower first
and clean ourselves.
Alright. You both go take a shower.
I will prepare lunch for you.
Come in.
Dad?
- My daughter.
- Father.
How are you? Feeling better?
Yes, Thank God.
But I'm still a bit weak.
How was your trip?
It was alright.
I really miss you.
I miss you, too.
Git.
You have to get better.
I know.
I'm trying my best to recover too.
That's more like it.
How are your studies?
They’re good. I have Arya helping me.
Arya, you should rest
after you're done eating.
I'm sure you must be tired
after driving all the way from Jakarta.
I'm fine. I'm not sleepy at all.
Inggit.
Can you help clean up after this?
I have to get your dad's medicine
at the pharmacy in Gondomanan.
Alright.
I can do it.
Do you even know where it is?
I can use the map.
Do you have the prescription?
- It's right behind you.
- Oh, okay.
- I'll go and get it now.
- Yeah.
Git, Arya cares so much
about our family.
You're so lucky to have him
as your husband.
Are you done?
Yeah. I'll do the dishes.
Download Asian Drama, Movies and Shows @ MkvDrama.Com
Can we talk outside, Mr. Arya?
How is he?
All I can say is we have
to pray for his health to improve.
Is there anything that should be done?
Like a surgery, maybe?
I'm worried
there will be complications...
if we perform any surgery
in this condition.
And hospital treatment is very limited
in this time.
Get some rest.
I'll take my leave, then.
Thanks. Sorry, I can't show you out.
Get some sleep, dad.
- Good night.
Mosquito?
You monkey.
So is it a monkey or mosquito?
A mosquito.
I think your mom forget
to put one in here.
Okay, I'll go look for it.
- Have you prayed?
- Yes.
That coffee must already be cold.
Let me make a fresh cup.
You don't have to. It's fine.
Where's Inggit?
She went outside to buy some
mosquito repellent for father's room.
Is it okay for her to go outside
at this hour?
It's fine. It's just nearby.
Thief! Thief! Help! Thief!
- Help!
- Inggit!
- Hey!
- Thief!
Thief!
Thief! Help!
Arya!
- Arya!
- Stay back, Inggit.
Help! Thief!
Thief...!
Oh, gosh! Oh, gosh! Arya, are you okay?
Oh, gosh! You're bleeding.
- Are you sure you're okay?
- I'm okay.
We have to treat your wound.
I'm sorry.
- Are you sure you're okay?
- I'm fine. Your wound...
The guy was wearing
a black leather jacket.
Short hair.
I think he's middle-aged, not too tall.
Okay. Let me call the others
and check the area.
Thank you, sir.
Oh no.
I don't understand this.
Why don't you want to go
to the hospital?
I don't know how to treat this.
We don't need to see a doctor.
But what if it gets infected?
No, it won't.
- How to...
- Rub it with alcohol first.
Use the cotton. Do it gently.
Okay.
Soak it first, and then press it
to my hand. Don't let it go.
- Or it will hurt more.
- Okay.
Are you sure?
Just press it to your hand?
Wait, wait, wait!
- What is it?
- Okay, now.
Gently.
Okay, now.
Please don't do that.
- You're scaring me.
- I'm fine. One more time.
- Really?
- Come on.
I haven't even touched it!
Are you doing it on purpose?
No, I thought you did.
- No!
- I thought I felt it.
- Can you please hold it?
- It hurts!
- Just press it.
- Done. Here.
I think we should take you to hospital.
- Okay, it's done.
- I have to apply the antiseptic.
Okay, hurry.
- Sorry.
- What are you sorry for?
What’s important is that you’re alright.
- Well, I mean...
- It's okay.
I shouldn't have gone out this late.
It’s your fault. Who would've known
something like this might happen?
The most important thing
is that you're safe.
I'm going to bandage it up now.
Wrap it one more time.
Okay, that's enough. I’ll do it myself.
- Sorry, I don't know how.
- It's okay.
Let me help. Here.
Please don't do this again.
What if you had gotten killed?
Who else should I die for
if not for you?
- We'll fix this at home.
- Yes.
Done. Let's go home.
♪Life at first feels
As beautiful as I imagined♪
♪Until you came
And disturbed this feeling♪
♪Nothing was ever wrong
There were no problems♪
♪Until you came and ruined it♪
♪I hate you♪
♪But my heart chooses love♪
♪Need to get away♪
♪Erase all traces of you♪
♪But life puts us together♪
♪You and I♪
♪Happy♪
♪Life at first feels
As beautiful as I imagined♪
♪Until you came
And disturbed this feeling♪
♪Nothing was ever wrong
There were no problems♪
♪Until you came and ruined it♪
Download Asian Drama, Movies and Shows @ MkvDrama.Com